<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Turismo Valledupar</string>
    <string name="Valledupar">Valledupar, one of the most colorful and joyful places on the coast, its people and cultural wealth allows us to enjoy many truly memorable places</string>
    <string name="ubicacionx">Where I am?</string>
    <string name="marker_detail_latlng">(%1$.2f, %2$.2f)</string>

    // main
    <string name="eventos">Events</string>
    <string name="hacer">What to do?</string>
    <string name="visitar">What to do?</string>
    <string name="recreacion">Recreation</string>
    <string name="region">Region</string>
    <string name="fiestas">night</string>
    <string name="iniciarSesion">Log in</string>

    //registrarse
    <string name="registrarse">Check in</string>
    <string name="cuenta">I already have an account</string>
    <string name="textUsuario">Enter your username</string>
    <string name="textClave">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="textClave2">Enter your new password</string>
    <string name="textCorreo">Write your email</string>
    <string name="olvidoPass">Forgot your password?</string>

    <string name="cambiarClave">Change Password</string>

    <string name="pruebaAtanques">It is the main settlement of the Kankuama ethnic group, located in the middle of the Chiscuinlla and Candela rivers. Its cobbled streets cross small hills and form rows of roads that communicate with each other</string>
    <string name="laMina"># 1 of 6 Outdoor Activities in Valledupar Outdoor activities, More outdoor activities</string>

    //que hacer
    <string name="natacion">swimming</string>
    <string name="parques">Parks</string>
    <string name="monumentos">Monuments</string>
    <string name="sitios">famous sites</string>

    // monumentos
    <string name="valle">i love Valledupar</string>
    <string name="valledupar">The strategy Yo Amo a Valledupar, leads the vallenatos to internalize in their hearts the sense of belonging to a city, beautiful, welcoming, cultural and musical; But it is not to love Valledupar, it is to demonstrate it, with a citizen culture, with care and cleanliness, speaking well of it and its people. With true love for this land full of charm, that we want to see in peace.r</string>
    <string name="poporos">The poporos</string>
    <string name="poporos2">The Colosseum is one of the few that has a movable roof. Built in the late 90s, it is located in front of the sculpture of Los Poporos. This sculpture pays tribute to the three indigenous ethnic groups that still inhabit the Sierra Nevada, such as the Arhuacos, the Koguis and the Arzarios.</string>
    <string name="ecce">Holy Ecce Homo</string>
    <string name="ecce2">El Santo Ecce Homo es el patrono de Valledupar. Una réplica de 30 metros, que vigila la ciudad desde el Cerro de las Antenas, es lugar de peregrinaje para devotos y meta para deportistas. Fue diseñada por el maestro colombiano Héctor Lombana, la estructura mide 35 metros de altura.</string>
    <string name="cacique">Cacique Upar</string>
    <string name="cacique2">To the south east of the city stands the imposing El Cacique Upar, a beautiful sculpture representative of our indigenous aborigines who defended this region from the Spanish invaders. Curiously, it owes the name of our city, because Valledupar is an acronym for: Valle del Cacique Upar. He was the maximum chief of the Chimilas, a tribe of the region and those who had to move to the Sierra Nevada to avoid their total exterminationr</string>


    //sitios insignes
    <string name="plaza">Plaza Alfonso Lopez</string>
    <string name="plaza2">It is the founding square of the city. Venue of the famous Tarima Francisco el hombre and cradle of the Vallenata Legend Festival, which was held there for several decades until it was insufficient to accommodate the tourists who visited us. By touring the houses that surround it, you can learn about the history of the city, reading the plaques on each one of them. Its earthenware, from above, represent the paths of life of the Arhuaca cosmogony. It is currently being remodeled by the municipal mayor office.</string>
    <string name="loperena">School Loperena</string>
    <string name="loperena2">it was created as a tribute to the memory of the vallenata heroine Doña María Concepción Loperena de Fernández de Castro, who rendered invaluable services to the independence of the Republic. Recognized as the Alma mater del Cesar for having trained most of the Departments leaders in the 20th century in their classrooms. In 1993, the facilities of the Colegio Nacional Loperena were declared National Monument of Colombia.
A special permit is required to enter from 8:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m.</string>
    <string name="mayo">1st of May square</string>
    <string name="mayo2">It is a park where you can enjoy, have fun and play. It is an attraction for children and adults alike. Concerts are held here since it has a wide platform and a large space. In addition, there is the monument of the guitars. This was installed on February 8, 2009 and is a tribute to the neighborhood festivities that start just the day after the Vallenato festival ends.
Public space.</string>
    <string name="gobernacion">Cesar Governorate</string>
    <string name="gobernacion2">The plaza has a flag park that has 27 27-meter-high poles on which the flags of each of the municipalities of the department of Cesar and Colombia fly. This recently renovated square is a green space for recreation that has several monuments that represent the idiosyncrasy of the region.Public space.</string>
    <string name="helado">Province park</string>
    <string name="helado2">Place where Carlos Vives is honored as ambassador of our culture and folklore, who is also the godfather of this beautiful place. It will be located where the Ice Cream Park is today. It will be connected to the Juglares roundabout and will have water sources. The DC6 plane, parked there for the enjoyment of children, will become a museum of the life and work of this great artist.Public space.</string>
    <string name="leyenda">Vallenata legend park</string>
    <string name="leyenda2">t is an architectural complex with an extension of 23 hectares, located north of the city of Valledupar, on the right bank of the Guatapurí river. Since 2004 the Vallenato Festival has been held here. It is an ecological, cultural, tourist and recreational site surrounded by bushes where the Compae Chipuco platform of the Cacique Upar Coliseum is located, with a capacity for 40,000 spectators. It is perhaps the best concert venue in the country.Free admission to all public from 8:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m.</string>
    <string name="novalito">Novalito Park</string>
    <string name="novalito2">Leisure place to the north of the city, it has a WIFI zone and a cycle route. It is host to many Micro-Soccer business championships. It is a good place to rest and enter the Historic Center of the city. It is located in the heart of one of the most traditional neighborhoods of the Vallenato cultural imaginary, from which it takes its name. Public space.</string>
    <string name="cortijos">Cortijos Park</string>
    <string name="cortijos2">Recreation place that has tennis courts, beach volleyball, synthetic soccer, bio-healthy park, basketball courts and multifunctional. It also has wide green spaces to delight in cool shades. This sunny landscape that always bathes the city, attracts many visitors to the park all the time.Public space.</string>

    //fiestas
    <string name="candelaria">Patronal Festival of La Candelaria</string>
    <string name="candelaria2">This festival takes place during the month of February, in the municipality of Becerril.</string>

    <string name="SanJuan">Patronal of San Juan Bosco</string>
    <string name="SanJuan2">Celebration and veneration of the patron saint of the municipality of Bosconia, San Juan Bosco. January 31 begins with a musical dawn.</string>

    <string name="acordeon">My Accordion Piece Festival</string>
    <string name="acordeon2">It is celebrated in the municipality of El Paso. The organizing board of this festival created this event to pay tribute each year to the composer and musician that no one forgets: Alejandro Durán.</string>

    <string name="ganadera">Valledupar livestock fair</string>
    <string name="ganadera2">It is generally celebrated in the month of August. Cesar is considered an eminently agricultural and livestock region.</string>

    <string name="festival">Vallenata Legend Festival</string>
    <string name="festival2">The Vallenata Legend Festival is celebrated in the city of Valledupar generally during the month of April.</string>

    <string name="cafe">Arhuaca Coffee and Backpack Festival</string>
    <string name="cafe2">It is celebrated in the municipality of Pueblo Bello in the month of July.</string>

    <string name="candefiesta">Nuestra Señora de la Candelaria</string>
    <string name="juanfiesta">San Juan Bosco</string>

    <string name="maratana">El establecimiento sirve un desayuno buffet.\n
La zona es ideal para practicar ciclismo. El Hotel Maranata Valledupar ofrece servicio de alquiler de coches.\n
El hotel alberga un centro de negocios y máquinas expendedoras de bebidas y aperitivos.\n
El Hotel Maranata Valledupar se encuentra a 5 km del aeropuerto Alfonso López Pumarejo, el más cercano. Se ofrece servicio de enlace con el aeropuerto por un suplemento.</string>

    <string name="sonesta">Este hotel moderno se encuentra a 4 km de la Plaza Alfonso López y cuenta con vistas panorámicas a la Sierra Nevada de Santa Marta. Hay WiFi gratuita y aparcamiento gratuito.\n
Las habitaciones del Sonesta Valledupar, de 5 estrellas, son amplias y tienen aire acondicionado, TV por cable, teléfono, minibar, tonos neutros, ventanas amplias y escritorio con silla ergonómica.\n
   El Sonesta Valledupar cuenta con zona de fitness y recepción abierta las 24 horas </string>

    <string name="tativan">Este hotel ofrece una piscina al aire libre, una terraza, un bar, un restaurante, un desayuno bufé, conexión Wi-Fi gratuita, 7 salas de conferencias y un centro de negocios.\n
Las habitaciones y suites del Hotel Tativan tienen baño privado, zona de estar, minibar y TV por cable. Además, hay un servicio de habitaciones.\n
La Sierra Restaurant ofrece platos nacionales e internacionales.\n En Los Junglares Bar podrá tomar una copa y un aperitivo.</string>

    <string name="mayales">El Hotel Mayales Plaza ofrece alojamiento con aire acondicionado en Valledupar. El establecimiento cuenta con restaurante, recepción 24 horas, servicio de habitaciones y WiFi gratuita en todas las instalaciones. El hotel dispone de habitaciones familiares.\n
Las habitaciones están equipadas con armario, TV de pantalla plana y baño privado.\n
El Hotel Mayales Plaza sirve un desayuno americano todas las mañanas.\n
El alojamiento dispone de terraza.\n
El Hotel Mayales Plaza ofrece servicio gratuito de enlace con el aeropuerto Alfonso López Pumarejo, situado a 6 km.</string>

    <string name="sicarare">El Hotel Sicarare se encuentra a solo 500 metros del ayuntamiento y cuenta con piscina cubierta. Se ofrece WiFi gratuita y desayuno.\n La avenida principal está a 200 metros.\n
Las habitaciones del Sicarare Hotel son amplias y están equipadas con aire acondicionado, TV por cable, minibar y hamacas.\n Algunas de ellas cuentan con zona de estar independiente y TV de plasma.\n
Todos los días se sirve un desayuno buffet en el bar.\n Hay un restaurante que prepara platos locales e internacionales.\n
El establecimiento dispone de piscina con tumbonas y tienda de belleza.</string>

</resources>